flcu.org 2015-03-15

# Florida Credit Union Privacy Policy & Disclosures | Florida Credit Union

###  Florida Credit Union’s Disclosures

Please click here to read Florida Credit Union’s Terms and Conditions of services available by and through our website, Online Banking, or Mobile Banking.

To access Florida Credit Union’s Member Service disclosures, please click here.

To access Florida Credit Union's Visa Credit Card disclosures, please [click here](https://www.flcu.org/assets/1/7/7-2013_Agreement_for_FDR.pdf).

To access the Consumer Account Agreement, please click here.

To access the Commercial Account Agreement, please click here.

To access the Error Resolution Notice, please click here.  

###  Florida Credit Union’s Privacy Policy

**What does Florida Credit Union do with your personal information?**

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

  * Social Security Number and Income
  * Account Number and Payment History
  * Credit History and Credit Scores

When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information, the reasons FCU chooses to share and whether you can limit this sharing.

Reasons we can share your personal information |  Does FCU Share? |  Can you limit this sharing?  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes** – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations or report to credit bureaus. |  Yes |  No  
**For our marketing purposes** – to offer our products and services to you |  Yes |  No  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** |  Yes |  No  
**For our affiliates’* everyday business purposes** – information about your transactions and experiences |  N/A |  N/A  
**For our affiliates’* everyday business purposes** – information about your creditworthiness |  N/A |  N/A  
**For our affiliates* to market to you** |  N/A |  N/A  
**For our non-affiliates** to market to you** |  N/A |  N/A  
  
**How does Florida Credit Union protect my personal information?**  
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

**How does Florida Credit Union collect my personal information?**  
We collect your personal information, for example, when you:

  * Open an Account or Deposit Money
  * Pay Your Bills or Apply for a Loan
  * Use Your Debit or Credit Card

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus.

**Why can’t I limit all sharing?**  
Federal law gives you the right to limit only:

  * Sharing for affiliates’* everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
  * Affiliates* from using your information to market to you
  * Sharing for non-affiliates** to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.

###  Important Information about Procedures for Opening a New Account

To help the government fight the funding of terrorism and money laundering activities, Federal law requires all financial institutions to obtain, verify and record information that identifies each person who opens an account. What this means for you: When you open an account, we will ask for your name, address, date of birth and other identifying documents.

You should know that credit bureaus are permitted to sell your name, address and other contact information to companies that wish to market to you their credit or insurance products or services.

You have the right to prohibit the use of your file with any credit reporting agency in connection with any transaction that you did not initiate. You may exercise this right by notifying Equifax Options, PO Box 740123, Atlanta, GA 30374-0123; TransUnion, Name Removal Option, PO Box 97328, Jackson, MS 39288; Experian Consumer OPT-OUT, 901 W. Bond, Lincoln, NE 68521; or call 1-888-5OPT-OUT (1-888-567-8688).

In addition, to stop telemarketers from calling you, you may enroll in the National Do Not Call Registry by calling 1-888-382-1222. By enrolling, telemarketers may not call you to sell goods or services unless you have a previous business relationship with them.

_*Definition of affiliates: Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. Florida Credit Union has no affiliates._

_** Definition of non-affiliates: Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. Florida Credit Union only works with companies that agree to maintain strong confidentiality protections and limit the use of the information we provide to FCU use only._
